{
  "questions": [
    {
      "question": "What is the airspeed velocity of an unladen swallow?",
      "correct": "African or European?",
      "incorrect1": "10 MPH",
      "incorrect2": "20 MPH",
      "incorrect3": "30 KM/H"
    },
    {
      "question": "How many licks does it take to get to the tootsie roll center of a tootsie pop?",
      "correct": "The world may never know",
      "incorrect1": "1",
      "incorrect2": "2",
      "incorrect3": "3"
    },
    {
      "question": "How you doin'?",
      "correct": "Aight",
      "incorrect1": "What?",
      "incorrect2": "Back off",
      "incorrect3": "Not aight"
    },
    {
      "question": "How many questions are in this quiz?",
      "correct": "10",
      "incorrect1": "1",
      "incorrect2": "100",
      "incorrect3": "As many as you believe there are"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is in my pocket?",
      "correct": "A pencil",
      "incorrect1": "The One Ring",
      "incorrect2": "A bag of crisps",
      "incorrect3": "Nothing"
    },
    {
      "question": "What language is my question database written in?",
      "correct": "JSON",
      "incorrect1": "How should I know?",
      "incorrect2": "Lisp",
      "incorrect3": "Magic"
    },
    {
      "question": "Can I have your number?",
      "correct": "Yes",
      "incorrect1": "No",
      "incorrect2": "No",
      "incorrect3": "No"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the greatest movie of all time?",
      "correct": "The Shawshank Redemption",
      "incorrect1": "Cheetah Girls",
      "incorrect2": "Care Bear Journey to Care-a-Lot",
      "incorrect3": "Birdemic"
    },
    {
      "question": "Which answer will you choose?",
      "correct": "The correct one",
      "incorrect1": "An incorrect one",
      "incorrect2": "A different incorrect one",
      "incorrect3": "The one pretending to be correct"
    },
    {
      "question": "Who is tired of writing questions?",
      "correct": "Josh",
      "incorrect1": "The NSA",
      "incorrect2": "Santa Clause",
      "incorrect3": "Bernie Sanders"
    },
    {
      "question": "How many frames of invincibility does Jigglypuff have after Rest?",
      "correct": "27",
      "incorrect1": "14",
      "incorrect2": "17",
      "incorrect3": "30"
    },
    {
      "question": "How many frame(s) of lagg occur after Peach float cancels?",
      "correct": "4",
      "incorrect1": "7",
      "incorrect2": "6",
      "incorrect3": "1"
    },
    {
      "question": "How many frames does Ganondorf's aerial down-B lagg?",
      "correct": "57",
      "incorrect1": "45",
      "incorrect2": "25",
      "incorrect3": "13"
    },
    {
      "question": "How many times can Fox multishine per second, given frame-perfect inputs?",
      "correct": "7",
      "incorrect1": "5",
      "incorrect2": "3",
      "incorrect3": "6"
    },
    {
      "question": "Who is the G.O.A.T. of Super Smash Bros. Melee?",
      "correct": "Mang0",
      "incorrect1": "Hungrybox",
      "incorrect2": "Leffen",
      "incorrect3": "Mew2King"
    },
    {
      "question": "What country was Dio hiding in during Stardust Crusaders?",
      "correct": "Egypt",
      "incorrect1": "United States",
      "incorrect2": "Germany",
      "incorrect3": "India"
    },
    {
      "question": "Erina pendleton thought her first kiss would be with Jonathan but instead,",
      "correct": "'It was me, DIO!'",
      "incorrect1": "'It was me, Zeppeli!'",
      "incorrect2": "'It was me, Jotaro!'",
      "incorrect3": "'It was me, Cars!'"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is Dio's father's name?",
      "correct": "Dario Brando",
      "incorrect1": "Jotaro Brando",
      "incorrect2": "Dario Joestar",
      "incorrect3": "William Zeppeli"
    },
    {
      "question": "Who was the leader of the pillar men?",
      "correct": "Cars",
      "incorrect1": "Santana",
      "incorrect2": "Whammu",
      "incorrect3": "Esidisi"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the name of Dio's stand?",
      "correct": "ZA WARUDO!",
      "incorrect1": "MAJISHANZU REDDO!",
      "incorrect2": "SUTA PURACHINA!",
      "incorrect3": "HAMITTO PAPURU!"
    },
    {
      "question": "What shape is the birthmark on the members of the Joestar bloodline?",
      "correct": "5-point star",
      "incorrect1": "4-point star",
      "incorrect2": "The letter 'J'",
      "incorrect3": "6-point star"
    },
    {
      "question": "What iconic accessory does Hestia wear in hit anime series Dungeon ni Deai wo Motomeru no wa Machigatteiru Barou ka",
      "correct": "Blue ribbon",
      "incorrect1": "Purple shoulderplates",
      "incorrect2": "Elucidator",
      "incorrect3": "Pokemon"
    },
    {
      "question": "Who is One Punch Man's sidekick",
      "correct": "A cyborg",
      "incorrect1": "Two Punch Man",
      "incorrect2": "Three Punch Man",
      "incorrect3": "2 cyborgs"
    },
    {
      "question": "In Cute High Earth Defense Club Love, what species does the alien helping the Cute High Earth Defense Club resemble?",
      "correct": "A koala",
      "incorrect1": "A hedgehog",
      "incorrect2": "A fish",
      "incorrect3": "A cute boy"
    },
    {
      "question": "In Koroku no Basket, what basketball move does Koroku use to defeat Yamata",
      "correct": "The vanishing shot",
      "incorrect1": "The vanishing pass",
      "incorrect2": "Maximumero overoodriiiiive",
      "incorrect3": "Boostooo"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is Pokemans",
      "correct": "An anime",
      "incorrect1": "Not an anime",
      "incorrect2": "A brand of decorative hedge ornaments",
      "incorrect3": "Alex Shockency's nickname in high school"
    },
    {
      "question": "Where is anime from",
      "correct": "Nippon",
      "incorrect1": "Japan",
      "incorrect2": "Germany",
      "incorrect3": "Filthy America"
    },
    {
      "question": "How many evil ex-boyfriends does Ramona Flowers have in the Scott Pilgrim series",
      "correct": "6",
      "incorrect1": "7",
      "incorrect2": "8",
      "incorrect3": "5"
    },
    {
      "question": "All four nations lived in harmony until the _____ nation attacked",
      "correct": "Fire",
      "incorrect1": "Earth",
      "incorrect2": "Water",
      "incorrect3": "Air"
    },
    {
      "question": "In Deathu no Notu, what does kira do after taking the potato chip?",
      "correct": "He eats it",
      "incorrect1": "He discards it",
      "incorrect2": "He writes its name in the Death Note",
      "incorrect3": "He doesn't eat it"
    },
    {
      "question": "In Pepe no Monogatori, why does Pepe run away from home?",
      "correct": "He didn't get his tendies",
      "incorrect1": "He eloped with a girl",
      "incorrect2": "He got a job and moved out",
      "incorrect3": "He doesn't run away from home"
    },
    {
      "question": "In Cutie Cute High School Girl FunTimes Cutie Cutes (How Can They Be This Cute?), what is the name of the Cutie Cute girl with green hair?",
      "correct": "Cutie Cute Crystal Genesis Y Ultimate",
      "incorrect1": "Cutie Cute Purple",
      "incorrect2": "Cutie Cute Omega X",
      "incorrect3": "Cutie Cute Green"
    },
    {
      "question": "In Fire Emblem, what is the major weakness of flying units?",
      "correct": "Wind magic and archers",
      "incorrect1": "Dragon units and Fire magic",
      "incorrect2": "Arcane magic and Burrowers",
      "incorrect3": "Walls and tall trees"
    },
    {
      "question": "In the Pheonix Wright series, what profession is Pheonix Wright?",
      "correct": "Defense Attourney",
      "incorrect1": "Plumber",
      "incorrect2": "Witcher",
      "incorrect3": "Prosciutto"
    },
    {
      "question": "In Dark Souls, which character wants the Chosen Undead to bring about the Age of Humanity?",
      "correct": "Kaathe",
      "incorrect1": "Gwyn",
      "incorrect2": "Smough",
      "incorrect3": "Prosciutto"
    },
    {
      "question": "In Pokemon, what does Brock change his frying pan into?",
      "correct": "A drying pan",
      "incorrect1": "A pokemon",
      "incorrect2": "Ash Ketchum",
      "incorrect3": "Satoshi"
    },
    {
      "question": "In Pokemon, what was Ash Ketchum's original name before it was tainted by being dubbed into English?",
      "correct": "Satoshi",
      "incorrect1": "A pokemon",
      "incorrect2": "Ash Ketchum",
      "incorrect3": "Ash Ketchup"
    },
    {
      "question": "Who isn't cool enough to believe anime is real life?",
      "correct": "Alex Shockency",
      "incorrect1": "Josh Fuller",
      "incorrect2": "Shigiru Miyamoto",
      "incorrect3": "Konata Izumi"
    },
    {
      "question": "Who is Josh Fuller's waifu?",
      "correct": "Konata Izumi",
      "incorrect1": "Taiga Aisaka",
      "incorrect2": "Jonathan Jostar",
      "incorrect3": "Ross McConnel"
    },
    {
      "question": "Who is Alex Shockency's waifu",
      "correct": "Alex Shockency does not have a waifu",
      "incorrect1": "Josh Fuller",
      "incorrect2": "Tiger Woods",
      "incorrect3": "Corey in the House"
    },
    {
      "question": "Who is a busta'?",
      "correct": "Corey in the House",
      "incorrect1": "Anime",
      "incorrect2": "Manga",
      "incorrect3": "Video games"
    },
    {
      "question": "In Undertale, what is the name of the first character you encounter?",
      "correct": "Flowey the Flower",
      "incorrect1": "Sans",
      "incorrect2": "Papyrus",
      "incorrect3": "Asgore"
    },
    {
      "question": "What tool does guy 2 use in dig champs?",
      "correct": "A pickaxe",
      "incorrect1": "A shovel",
      "incorrect2": "A drill",
      "incorrect3": "A knife"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the name of Meat Boy's girlfriend in Super Meat Boy?",
      "correct": "Bandage Girl",
      "incorrect1": "Meat Girl",
      "incorrect2": "Meat Boy",
      "incorrect3": "Meat Man"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the name of Meat Boy's nemesis in Super Meat Boy?",
      "correct": "Dr. Fetus",
      "incorrect1": "Vegetarian Man",
      "incorrect2": "Meat Girl",
      "incorrect3": "Dr. Horrible"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the name of Squidward's nemesis in the anime Spongebob Squarepants?",
      "correct": "Squilliam Fancyson",
      "incorrect1": "His clarinet",
      "incorrect2": "His nose",
      "incorrect3": "Fine dining"
    },
    {
      "question": "In hit anime series Harry Potter, what is the shape of the scar on Harry Potter's forehead?",
      "correct": "Lightning bolt",
      "incorrect1": "Pickles the kitten",
      "incorrect2": "Emma Watson",
      "incorrect3": "flaming skull with, like, snakes all over"
    },
    {
      "question": "In anime Yona of the Dawn, what is Yona's name?",
      "correct": "Yona",
      "incorrect1": "Bona",
      "incorrect2": "Flona",
      "incorrect3": "Zona"
    },
    {
      "question": "In Monthly Girl Nozeki-kun, what is the main character's iconic headwear?",
      "correct": "Polka dot bow",
      "incorrect1": "Flaming skull with, like, snakes all over",
      "incorrect2": "Helm of death",
      "incorrect3": "Cat ears"
    },
    {
      "question": "What does CS stand for?",
      "correct": "Computer Science",
      "incorrect1": "Counter Strike",
      "incorrect2": "Cowden Syndrome",
      "incorrect3": "Congregation of the Missionaries of St. Charles"
    },
    {
      "question": "What symbol is used in binary?",
      "correct": "0",
      "incorrect1": "2",
      "incorrect2": "A",
      "incorrect3": ":)"
    }
  ]
}